savorysweetlife.com 2019-03-15

# Privacy Policy | Savory Sweet Life

Privacy Policy

At Savory Sweet Life https://savorysweetlife.com, we respect your privacy and consider it to be very important. This privacy policy describes in detail what types of personally identifiable information is collected and how it’s used.

What Information is Collected

Log Files: Like many other websites, we automatically use log files which automatically collects certain information about log visitors to the site – standard practice. Information collected includes your IP address, browser type, date/time stamp, referring websites, operating system, and links clicked.

Cookies: Savory Sweet Life uses cookies, which store small data files on your browser which expire when you close your browser. This is to provide you with a more customized or personalized experience on our website based on your browser. The cookies will stay on your browser until deleted.

Email addresses: If you subscribe to receive new blog posts via email, your email address will be stored in our system. This information is not used for any other purposes. At any time if you wish to unsubscribe from receiving new posts, click the “unsubscribe” link that appears at the bottom of any email.

Information You Voluntarily Submit

Anytime you leave a comment, you are voluntarily submitting information such as your name and email.  Although this information is collected, it is not used for any purpose than the user’s intended purpose – to leave a comment. Along with your name and email, your IP address will be recorded along with your website address should you choose to submit one on the comment form.

How Your Information is Used

The information collected as stated in this privacy policy may be used to respond to your comments and questions, provide you with user support, to anonymously track analytics data from your cookies as well as measure advertising metrics on this website. Analytics programs include Google, Quantcast, MediaVine, and StatCounter.

Information Collected by Others

Our Advertising Partners: Our website’s advertising and affiliate partners may use cookies on our site. Our partners include Amazon.com and MediaVine. Each of these third parties provide have their own Privacy Policy for the use of your personal information.

MediaVine uses cookies to serve ads based on your visits to this site. Their ad servers and networks use banners and links automatically receiving your IP address.  Savory Sweet Life is an affiliate of Amazon Services LLC Associates Program. Amazon’s affiliate advertising program allows this website to earn advertising fees through links to Amazon.com. These links track referrals to their Affiliate program to calculate commissions on these sales.

Children’s Information

Savory Sweet Life does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 16. Please contact us immediately at savorysweetlife@gmail.com if you believe we have collected this information. We will remove it immediately.

Privacy Policy Terms

By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms. If you have any questions about our privacy policy please contact savorysweetlife@gmaamil.com.

This privacy policy was last updated on May 14, 2018.
